Finding aid for University Herbarium (University of Michigan) Records, 1744-1745, 1851-1981, and 2001-2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Bartlett, Harley Harris, 1744-1855; 1875-1959
  - Correspondence and Associated Materials, 1875-1959
    - A
      - Asa Gray Bulletin, 1951-1958
        - Larsen, Lillian A., 1953 (Box 2)
        - Laughlin, Emma E., 1952 (Box 2)
        - Launching A.G.B., 1951- (Box 2)
        - Manuscripts (Box 2)
        - Notes (Box 2)
        - Rogers, C. Marvin, 1952 (Box 2)
        - Schairer, Lloyd, 1955 (Box 2)
        - Scott, Dorothea, 1955 (Box 2)
        - Simpson, Elizabeth, 1952 (Box 2)
        - Stevens, O.A., 1953-1955 (Box 2)
        - Subscriptions (Box 2)
        - Swingle, Maude K., 1952 (Box 2)
        - Thompson, Paul, 1952 (Box 2)
        - Vernon, C.C., 1955 (Box 2)
        - Walker, Egbert H., 1952-1957 (Box 2)
        - Zahniser, Howard, 1953 (Box 2)
      - Asham, D., 1928 (Box 2)
        (student inquiry)
      - Ashe, W. Allard (Box 2)
      - Ashley, Allen (Box 2)
      - Atkins, Ogell A., 1946 (Box 2)
        (response to inquiry re position)
      - Atkinson, W. Eugene, 1938 (Box 2)
      - Atomic Energy Commission, 1950 (Box 2)
        (effects of radioactivity)
      - Atwell, C.B., 1928 (Box 2)
        (recommending Dale & F.J. Hermann)
      - Austin, J. Perry, 1929-1938 (Box 2)
      - Autographs (Box 2)
      - Avery, George S., 1937 (Box 2)
      - Avery, S.D., 1948 (Box 2)
        (mosquito breeding habitats)
      - Ayres, W.L., 1948 (Box 2)
        (re position at Purdue-Sparrow)
    - B
      - Baar, Harold L., 1957 (Box 2)
        ("Wadei"-Philippines)
      - Babcock, Ernest B., 1916 (Box 2)
        (walnut)
      - Bach, Doris A., 1934 (Box 2)
      - Bach, Ellen B., 1923 (Box 2)
        (amateur collector and grower)
      - Bacher, J.G., 1947 (Box 2)
        (Kingdon Ward exped.)
      - Bachman, Werner E., 1937 (Box 2)
      - Bacigalupi, Rimo, 1945 (Box 2)
        (A.F. collecting; see also A.G.B.)
      - Backus, Howard P. (Box 2)
      - Bacon, Robert L. (Box 2)
      - Badger, Richard G., 1933 (Box 2)
      - Bailey, B.A. deVere, 1941 (Box 2)
      - Bailey, Cecil W., 1937 (Box 2)
        (W.P.A.-Kalkaska Co.)
      - Bailey, Irving W., 1939 (Box 2)
        (1947-50 wood)
      - Bailey, Liberty Hyde, 1915 (Box 2)
        (1925-49)
      - Bailey, Willard F., 1936 (Box 2)
        (fossil spores)
      - Baits, Vera, 1944 (Box 2)
        (U of M Regent)
      - Baker, Charles F., 1909-1910 (Box 2)
        (plant collections)
      - Baker, Richard, 1944 (Box 2)
        (Guayule)
      - Baker, W.B., 1946 (Box 2)
      - Bald, F. Clever, 1945-1946 (Box 2)
        (additions to Univ. War Collection)
      - Baldwin, John T., 1938-1957 (Box 2)
        (see also Guggenheim-B.A. Moe)
      - Baldwin, K.F. (Box 2)
        (see Philippines-University)
      - Bartlett-Santos Exchange (Box 2)
      - Ball, Carlton R., 1925-1940 (Box 2)
        (willows)
      - Bank, Theodore P., 1945-1947 (Box 2)
        (A.F. collecting, Alaska; student)
      - Banking, Misc., 1931-1941 (Box 2)
        (personal)
      - Banks, Edgar J., 1925 (Box 2)
        (Babylonian tablets)
      - Barbeau, Marius, 1951 (Box 2)
        (Indian captivities, genealogy)
      - Barber, H.S., 1921 (Box 2)
        (old journals)
      - Barbour, K.M., 1956 (Box 2)
        (Fire & Prim. Agr.)
      - Barbour, Thomas, 1945 (Box 2)
        (coop. with Harvard re Atkins)
      - Barker, E.F., 1945 (Box 2)
        (exchange of letters between E.F.B.)
      - Barnard, Myra L., 1956 (Box 2)
        (linguistics)
      - Barnhart, John H., 1925 (Box 2)
        (re books)
      - Barnouw, Adriaan J., 1941 (Box 2)
        (see East Indies Inst.; Southeast)
      - Barr, S., 1944 (Box 2)
      - Barrau, Jacques, 1956-1957 (Box 2)
      - Barrett, Col. David D., 1950 (Box 2)
        (stamps; radioactive areas)
      - Barrett, Leonard T. (Box 2)
        (see Natural Areas)
      - Barrett, O.W., 1919 (Box 2)
        (palm sugars)
      - Barretto, Carlos, 1948 (Box 2)
      - Bartholomew, Elam, 1910 (Box 2)
        (Rhus)
      - Bartholomew, George A., 1947 (Box 2)
        (position, U. Philippines)
      - Bartlett, Clifford, 1907-1948 (Box 2)
        (personal-brother)
      - Bartlett, Forrest, 1942-1945 (Box 2)
        (personal-nephew)
      - Bartlett, Frances (Mrs. Clifford-), 1936 (Box 2)
        (personal-sister-in-law)
      - Bartlett, Harley H., 1905-1959
        - Appointments, 1915-1925 (Box 2)
          (9 items)
        - Bibliography, 1905-1959 (Box 2)
          (4 items)
        - Biographical information, 1909-1955 (Box 2)
          (21 items)
        - Honors (Box 2)
        - Journal, November-December 1918 (Box 2)
          (8 entries, Sumatra)
        - Journal, January-December 1926 (Box 2)
          (19 entries, Asahan-Formosa)
        - Journal, April-May 1927 (Box 2)
          (Asahan to Toba, Pargambuan to Sacred Mountain of the Batak)
        - Journal, 1935 (Box 3)
        - Journal, 1940-1941 (Box 3)
        - Journal, 1943 (Box 3)
        - Newspaper clippings, 1942-44 Argentina (Box 3)
        - Newspaper clippings, 1947 (Box 3)
          (Philippine Univs.)
        - Personal library (Box 3)
        - Personal photographs (Box 3)
          (see also photographic file)
        - Professorship, account-R. McVaugh (Box 3)
        - Prospective articles, 1952 (Box 3)
      - Bartlett, Harriet Potter ("Mama"), 1907-40, personal-family (Box 3)
      - Bartlett, Hazel, 1909-1950 (Box 3)
        (personal-sister)
      - Bartlett, Jonathan Hodgkin ("Dad"), 1907-25, personal-family (Box 3)
      - Bartlett, Mary Alice, 1928-1947 (Box 3)
        (personal-Mrs. Fred Hunt)
      - Bartlett, Rachel, 1928 (Box 3)
        (1942-43 personal-daughter of Clifford)
      - Barton, Bruce, 1956 (Box 3)
        (eugenics)
      - Bartram, Edwin B., 1930-1947 (Box 3)
        (mosses, A.F. collecting)
      - Baten, W.D., 1936 (Box 3)
        (statistics)
      - Bates, John M., 1910 (Box 3)
      - Bateson, William, 1922 (Box 3)
        (re visit to Ann Arbor)
      - Baumann-Bodenheim, Marcel G., 1954 (Box 3)
        (re speaking at U of M)
      - Baxter, Dow V., 1921-1947 (Box 3)
      - Baxter, Dow V., 1944 (Box 3)
        (Men in Service)
      - Bazuin, Clayton W., 1939 (Box 3)
      - Beard, Eleanor Cooke, 1922-1936 (Box 3)
      - Beasley, Ben J., 1925; 1939 (Box 3)
        (palm leaf book)
      - Beattie, R. Kent, 1928 (Box 3)
        (Formosa)
      - Bechtel, Arthur W., 1955 (Box 3)
      - Bechtol, L.A., 1945 (Box 3)
        (orchids)
      - Becker, George G. (Box 3)
        (see U.S. Department of Agriculture-Bur. Entomology)
      - Beetle, Alan A., 1946 (Box 3)
        (South American-collections)
      - Behnke, Curtis d., 1948 (Box 3)
        (Creosote bush-biochem.)
      - Belcher, Robert O., 1946-1955 (Box 3)
      - Bell, Walter A., 1929; 1945 (Box 3)
        (Sporangites)
      - Benary, Heinrich, 1912 (Box 3)
        (Oenothera)
      - Benedict, Ralph C., 1916 (Box 3)
        (reprint exchange; see also: Heller, B.)
      - Bennett, Ralph E., 1948 (Box 3)
        (re Bacteriology Dept.; see also Melchens, L.E.)
      - Benson, Lyman, 1946-1951 (Box 3)
        (positions; Lemnaceae)
      - Bentall, Ray, 1939 (Box 3)
      - Benton, Guy Potter, 1922 (Box 3)
        (re: Maranon, Philippines)
      - Berg, Clifford, 1946-1952 (Box 3)
      - Bergquist, S.G., 1934; 1952 (Box 3)
      - Berkeley Photographic Prints (Box 3)
      - Berkheimer, David, 1951 (Box 3)
        (oak)
      - Berlin, Theodore, 1946 (Box 3)
        (Association U of M Scientists, announcement and note in reply)
      - Bernardo, Gabriel A., 1936-1947 (Box 3)
        (Philippines-library; see Philippines-Hayden Memorial Library; Rockefeller Foundation; Philippine Foundation of America)
      - Besley, Lowell, 1954 (Box 3)
        (big trees)
      - Bessey, Charles E., 1911 (Box 3)
        (Populus)
      - Bessey, Ernst A., 1921-1955 (Box 3)
        (botanist, Mich. State, see also S.I.-Biographical,)
      - "Bett", 1944 (Box 3)
        (personal-cousin, Conn.)
      - Betts, G.L., 1936 (Box 3)
        ("education")
      - Betty, 1939 (Box 3)
        (personal-niece (?))
      - Beyer, H. Otley, 1936; 1948 (Box 3)
      - Bibby, F.F., 1947 (Box 3)
        (re position-U. Philippines)
      - Bicknell, Alice K., 1946 (Box 3)
      - Bicknell, Eugene P., 1916 (Box 3)
      - Bicknell, John W., 1926; 1938 (Box 3)
        (rubber, Sumatra)
      - Biggar, Dr. & Mrs. Robert J., 1946-1947 (Box 3)
      - Bill, ? (wife Cathy), 1952 (Box 3)
      - Billington, Cecil, 1930; 1932 (Box 3)
      - Bilon, Martin, 1920-1946 (Box 3)
        (gardener)
      - Bingham, Marjorie T., 1939-1947 (Box 3)
        (also under A.G.B.; Michigan United Conservation Clubs; Michigan Wildflower Association)
      - Biological Abstracts, 1937-1945 (Box 3)
      - Boak, H.S.R., 1932 (Box 3)
        (card from Egypt)
      - "Bob", 1944 (Box 3)
        (re pictures taken at Leon)
      - Bocobo, Jorge, 1936 (Box 3)
      - Boettcher, Norman H., 1936 (Box 3)
        (bot. research expeds.)
      - Bogusch, Edwin R., 1946 (Box 3)
        (re positions)
      - Boland, William A., 1934-1937 (Box 3)
        (naturalization; placement)
      - Bold, Harold C., 1932-1956 (Box 3)
      - Bolton, Herbe, 1945 (Box 3)
      - Bomhard, Miriam, 1937; 1949 (Box 3)
        (palms)
      - Bonar, Lee, 1935 (Box 3)
        (notice of death of Dr. Holman)
      - Bonner, Campbell, 1930 (Box 3)
      - Bonner, Ethel, 1926; 1928 (Box 3)
      - Bonner, Frances, 1918 (Box 3)
        (personal-A.A.)
      - Bonner, Gilbert, 1956 (Box 3)
      - Bonner, Sue G., 1931 (Box 3)
        (Vaxactum, Peten, Guatemala-personal)
      - Book dealers, 1912-1959
        - Blackwell's, 1959 (Box 3)
          (Fire & Prim. Agr.,3 items)
        - Brill, E.J., 1936 (Box 3)
          (2 items)
        - Cornwall's, 1939 (Box 3)
          (Central America, 1 item)
        - Dulan & Co., 3 items (Box 3)
        - Dultz & Co., 6 items (Box 3)
        - Gannon, Thomas J., 1950 (Box 3)
          (1 item, Loudon. Trees & Shrubs of Britain)
        - Gilhofer & Ranschburg, 2 items (Box 3)
        - Goldston, Edward, 1926 (Box 3)
          (3 items)
        - Grant, John, 1926 (Box 3)
          (1 item)
        - Heffner, W., 1936-1938 (Box 3)
        - Heller, F. Thomas, 1951 (Box 3)
        - Hiersemann, Karl W., 1926-1936 (Box 3)
          (6 items)
        - Knowles, John H., 1932 (Box 3)
        - Lowdermilk, W. H. & Co., 1928 (Box 3)
        - "Manila Filatelica", R. Garcia 1 item (Box 3)
        - Nijhoff, Martinus, 1926-1952 (Box 3)
        - Perkins, Thos., 1922 (Box 3)
        - Tuttle, Charles E. Co., 1950 (Box 3)
        - Universum Book Export Co. Inc., 1936 (Box 3)
          (letter re Mrs. J.B. Pollock)
        - Weg, Max, 1912-1913 (Box 3)
          (5 items)
        - Weigel, Oswald, 1912 (Box 3)
        - Wheldon & Wesley, 1934-1939 (Box 3)
      - Book plates, ±1914 collection (Box 3)
      - Boot, David H., 1923 (Box 3)
        (Botanical Gardens-drug plants)
      - Bor, Norman L., 1955 (Box 3)
      - Bornmuller, Joseph F.N. (Box 3)
      - Boston Society of Natural History, Secretary, 1945 (Box 3)
      - Botanical Abstracts, 1917-1947 (Box 3)
      - Botanical Gazette, 1928; 1951 (Box 3)
      - Botanical Society of America, 1916-1957 (Box 3)
        (also Nat. Herb. & Am. J. Bot.)
      - Botanists-Miscellaneous clippings (Box 3)
      - Botany Department, 1916-1946 (Box 4)
        - Budgets, 1937-1947 (Box 4)
        - Class enrollments, 1934-1945 (Box 4)
        - Directories (Box 4)
        - Dissertation reviews (Box 4)
        - Graduate students, 1934-1941 (Box 4)
        - Historical interest (?), 1916-1946 (Box 4)
        - Journal Club, 1919-1940 (Box 4)
        - Research in Progress, 1939-1942 (Box 4)
      - Bougham, Walter, 1933 (Box 4)
        (collections-Sumatra)
      - Bouin, P., 1923 (Box 4)
      - Bowers, Neal M., 1958 (Box 4)
        (Fire & Prim Agr.)
      - Bowles, Gordon T., 1945-1950 (Box 4)
        (N.R.C., see also Tsiu, You-Wen)
      - Bowmaker, P.A., 1955-1956 (Box 4)
      - Boyd, J.H.H., 1910 (Box 4)
        (Nursery)
      - Boyden, Margery, 1943; 1953 (Box 4)
      - Brackett, E.E., 1947 (Box 4)
        (U. Philippines faculty)
      - Bradford, Lester E., 1954 (Box 4)
      - Bradley, George W., 1945 (Box 4)
        (student application)
      - Bradley, John G., 1936 (Box 4)
      - Bradshaw, Mary Helen, 1942-1944 (Box 4)
        (personal-Ann Arbor, daughter of John B., prof. of mathematics)
      - Brainerd, Egra, 1921 (Box 4)
        (Rubus)
      - Braley, Berton, "poem" (Box 4)
      - Brand, Donald D., 1948 (Box 4)
        (Research in Mexico)
      - Brandenburg, Arthur H., 1940 (Box 4)
        (music, hospitality)
      - Brandes, E.W., 1940-1946 (Box 4)
        (guayule-B.P.I., see also Santos, J.V.; White, Arnold; & photographs in Palms Notes & photos)
      - Bravo, Helia, 1934 (Box 4)
        (plant exchange)
      - Bray, William L., 1929 (Box 4)
        (Inquiry and letter of recommendations)
      - Bredvold, Louis I. (Box 4)
      - Breitung, August J. request for reprint (Box 4)
      - Bremecamp, Cornelis E.B., 1938; 1940 (Box 4)
        (Rubiaceae)
      - Brierley, William B., (photographic file) (Box 4)
      - Briggs, Lyman J., 1948 (Box 4)
        (electroculture)
      - Briggs, Robert P., 1946-1948 (Box 4)
        (house-move; dept. research; see also Natural Areas & Whites Woods)
      - Brigham, Edward M., 1937-, arboretum-Battle Creek (Box 4)
      - Briscoe, E. Florence, 1939-1940 (Box 4)
        (student applicant)
      - Britton, Max E., 1948 (Box 4)
        (reprint request)
      - Brodie, Harold J., 1932-1954 (Box 4)
        (Former student; see also Vandendries, Biog. A.G.B.)
      - Bronk, Detler W., 1947 (Box 4)
        (N.R.C.)
      - Brooks, Maurice G., 1939 (Box 4)
        (Pteridophytes of W.Va.)
      - Brooks, S.C., 1934; 1944 (Box 4)
        (Bill Drew; Guayule)
      - Brooks, Mrs. S.T. (Betty Watt), 1937 (Box 4)
        (plant collection)
      - Brooks, Travis, 1946 (Box 4)
        (assistantship)
      - Brotherton, Wilbur, 1919-1936 (Box 4)
        (peas, etc.)
      - Brouwer, H.A., 1922 (Box 4)
      - Brown, Charles H. (Box 4)
        (see Philippines-J.R.H. Memorial Library)
      - Brown, Clair A., 1928-1952 (Box 4)
        (collections)
      - Brown, G.M., 1924 (Box 4)
        (collecting for Garden)
      - Brown, H.P. (Box 4)
        (see West, Gladys F.)
      - Brown, Mrs. H.W., 1938 (Box 4)
        (see Herb. Soc. of Amer.)
      - Brown, Monroe S., 1945 (Box 4)
      - Brown, Richard M. (Box 4)
        (see S.I. Historical-Oregon)
      - Brown, William H., 1937 (Box 4)
        (Philos. Soc. grant)
      - Browning, A.J., 1955 (Box 4)
      - Bruce, David (Box 4)
        (see USDA-Forest Service)
      - Bruneau, Homer F., 1945 (Box 4)
      - Buakeu, Manuel, 1946-1947 (Box 4)
        (Philippines library)
      - Buchanan, George E., 1925 (Box 4)
        (Alaska)
      - Buchholz, John T., 1937-1947 (Box 4)
        (A.A.A.S.; Podocarpus)
      - Buckman, H.H., 1921 (Box 4)
        (request for info.)
      - Budowski, Gerardo, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Buechner, Helmut K., 1959 (Box 4)
      - Buell, Mrs. F.D., 1948 (Box 4)
        (Inst. Int. Educ.; see also Wood, Grace L. & Tsui, You-en)
      - Bujak, B.J., 1937 (Box 4)
      - Bull. Torr. Bot. Club (Rickett), 1940 (Box 4)
      - Bullard, Charles, 1910 (Box 4)
        (Sphagnum)
      - Bunker, Frank F., 1936 (Box 4)
        (Carnegie-publication)
      - Bunting, F.C., 1944 (Box 4)
        (censorship -- stamps)
      - Burd, E.M., 1928 (Box 4)
        (peat deposit)
      - Burdick, B.F., 1942-1944 (Box 4)
        (Panama Canal)
      - Burkart, Arturo, 1943-1944 (Box 4)
        (Argentina)
    - C
      - Cain, Stanley A., 1945-1957 (Box 4)
        (violets; pollen atlas, Botanical Gardens)
      - Cake, W. Elwood, 1936-1949 (Box 4)
        (Sumatra Rahmat collections; position for Chi Chang Hwan)
      - Calderon, Cesar Vargas, 1956 (Box 4)
      - Caldervilla, J.M., 1944-1945 (Box 4)
      - Caldwell, Ralph M., 1949 (Box 4)
        (recommendations for S. Shapiro & T. Musik)
      - Calvin, John W., 1919 (Box 4)
        (pigmentation in brown corn)
      - Cambosco Scientific Co., 1940 (Box 4)
      - Cameron, George C., 1952 (Box 4)
      - Camp, Wendel H., 1940; 1947 (Box 4)
      - Campa, Arthur L., 1951 (Box 4)
        (plant lore)
      - Campbell, Douglas H., 1949 (Box 4)
      - Campbell, Oscar J., 1947 (Box 4)
        (position at U. Philippines)
      - Campbell, Mrs. Ralph, 1949 (Box 4)
        (genealogy)
      - Campbell, T., 1955 (Box 4)
      - Campbell, Thomas N., 1951 (Box 4)
        (Tamaulipas flora)
      - "Candy", 1948 (Box 4)
        (personal-Hawaii)
      - Cantrall, Irving J., 1940 (Box 4)
        (Hus library)
      - Caram, Marguerite, 1955 (Box 4)
      - Cardenas, Martin, 1956 (Box 4)
      - Carillo, Luis A., 1950 (Box 4)
        (Guatemala)
      - Carino, Francisco, 1947 (Box 4)
        (Philippine education)
      - Carlson, Harve J., 1949-1950 (Box 4)
        ("drug plants")
      - Carlson, Margery C., 1946-1948 (Box 4)
        (plant collections; Flora of China)
      - Carnegie institute, 1934-1952 (Box 4)
        (publications: Lundell, Bartlett)
      - Carothers, Neil, 1947 (Box 4)
        (Univ. Philippines staff)
      - Carow, J., 1945-1946 (Box 4)
      - Carpenter, C.A., 1944 (Box 5)
        (cotton-Argentina)
      - Lanzar-Carpio, Maria V.D., 1945-1949 (Box 5)
      - Carr, Alfred, B., 1945 (Box 5)
        (Cinchona)
      - Carr, Edward R., 1939 (Box 5)
        (real estate-Washington, D.C. (personal business))
      - Carson, Arthur L., 1957 (Box 5)
        (Philippines educ.)
      - Carson, Elizabeth, 1926 (Box 5)
        (re Sumatra trip)
      - Cartledge, J.L., 1936 (Box 5)
        (re position)
      - Case, E.C., 1936; 1954 (Box 5)
        (biographical)
      - Case, Frederick W., 1945-1950 (Box 5)
        (A.F. collecting & related items)
      - Case, H.C.M., 1947 (Box 5)
        (U. Philippines staff)
      - Cathelia, 1936 (Box 5)
        (personal-niece ?)
      - Cattell, Jacques, 1945 (Box 5)
        ("Science")
      - Cattell, Ware, "The Washington Scientist" (Box 5)
      - Cavanaugh, John, 1916 (Box 5)
        (re E.L. Greene)
      - Cense, A.A., 1957 (Box 5)
      - Central High School, Detroit, 1920 (Box 5)
        (request for lecture)
      - Chan, Ruth (Box 5)
        (see Wang, Lucy C.)
      - Chand, Rup (Box 5)
        (see W. Koelz; B.D. Thuma)
      - Chandonnet, Z.L., 1909-1915 (Box 5)
        (plant list & 8 letters from Z.L.C.)
      - Chang, Ying-Pe, 1949-1955 (Box 5)
        (student; wood)
      - Chapin, James P., 1956 (Box 5)
      - Chapline, W.R. (Box 5)
      - Chapman, Dorothy, 1946 (Box 5)
        (Lemna; Cuba)
      - Chapman, James W., 1936-1948 (Box 5)
        (plant collecting; Philippine libraries-reconstruction)
      - Chaput, William, 1945 (Box 5)
      - Chase, Agnes, (1910(?)-1959) (Box 5)
        (see also Santos, J.V.)
      - Chase, E. Winifred B., biographical material (Box 5)
      - Chatterjee, D., 1955-1956 (Box 5)
        (books; Dioscorea)
      - Chatterji, M.D., 1957 (Box 5)
      - Chatters, Roy M., 1939 (Box 5)
        ("siliceous skeletons" in wood)
      - Chaturvedi, M.D., 1957 (Box 5)
      - Cheadle, Vernon, 1945 (Box 5)
      - Chen, Shan Ming, 1940 (Box 5)
      - Chickering, A.M., 1928-1947 (Box 5)
        (botanist-Albion College)
      - "China Clipper", 1949; 1959 (Box 5)
        (philately)
      - China Colleges (Box 5)
        (see Wong, Cheong-uin)
      - "China Flora", 1946-1947 (Box 5)
        (plans for Flora of China with E.H. Walker; see also Walker, E.H.)
      - Correspondence & proposals (Box 5)
      - "China Welfare Appeal", 1951 (Box 5)
        (protest)
      - Chittenden, F.J., acknowledging reprint (Box 5)
      - Chou, Donald (Ting-Kwei Chou), 1944 (Box 5)
        (student-nephew of Ruth Chou)
      - Chou, Ruth (R.Ciu; Chen-Ying Chou), 1940-49, student (Box 5)
      - Chrysler, Mintin A., 1944 (Box 5)
        (Botrychium)
      - Chung, In-Cho, 1947-1956 (Box 5)
        (student-grasses)
      - Chung, Tae-Hyon, 1954-1955 (Box 5)
        (oaks-Korea, Schramm-Univ. Penna.)
      - Churchill, Irving L., 1948-1949 (Box 5)
      - Chute, R.M., 1945 (Box 5)
      - Clarendon Nursery Co., 1924 (Box 5)
        (plums)
      - Clark, Delbert, 1938 (Box 5)
        (appreciation)
      - Clark, Ernest D., 1913 (Box 5)
      - Clark, Mrs. Fred F., double-flowered bloodroot (Box 5)
      - Clark, Fred R., 1921-1946 (Box 5)
      - Clark, Herbert C., 1940-1945 (Box 5)
        (Panama)
      - Clark, Hugh M., 1944 (Box 5)
      - Clark, Larry & Margaret, appreciation-A.A. (Box 5)
      - Clark, Victor S., 1936 (Box 5)
      - Clark, 4.J., 1945 (Box 5)
      - Clary, J.M., 1945 (Box 5)
        (philately; A.F. collecting)
      - Clausen, Jens, 1947 (Box 5)
        (recommendations: Lewry, Hovanitz,)
      - Clausen, Robert T., 1941-1945 (Box 5)
        (Pachyrrhizus)
      - Clay, Floyd, 1954-1955 (Box 5)
      - Cleland, Ralph E., 1928-1948 (Box 5)
        (heterogametism, etc., see also Oehlkers, F.)
      - Clemens, Mary Strong, 1910-1953
        (letters & photographs)
        - 1912-1919 (Box 5)
          (Philippines, Calif.)
        - 1920-1929 (Box 5)
          (Calif., Ore., Philippines, Borneo, Sarawak)
        - 1930-1939 (Box 5)
          (Edinburgh, Holland, N.Y., Borneo, Java, New Guinea, Fiuschofen, Morobe)
        - 1940-1949 (Box 5)
        - Joseph C. Arthur (Purdue), 1918-1931 (Box 5)
        - Ellsworth Bethel (Colo., Calif.), 1910-1925 (Box 5)
        - W.C.Blasdale (Calif.), 1918-1922 (Box 5)
        - Agnes Chase (BPI), 1937-1953 (Box 5)
        - E.B.Copeland (Calif.), 1936-1948 (Box 5)
        - Otto Degener (Hawaii), 1951 (Box 5)
        - Carroll W. Dodge (Brown, Harvard, St. Louis), 1918-1948 (Box 5)
        - Alice Eastwood (Calif.), 1918-1936 (Box 5)
        - C.X. Furtado (Singapore), 1929-1955 (Box 5)
        - A.O.Garrett (Utah), 1918-1940 (Box 5)
        - M.R.Henderson (Singapore), 1934- (Box 5)
        - Albert W. Herre (Calif.), 1942-1951 (Box 5)
        - A.S.Hitchcock (Smithsonian), 1928-1935 (Box 5)
        - R.E.Holttum (Singapore), 1929-1952 (Box 5)
        - Herbert S. Jackson (Purdue), 1919-1928 (Box 5)
        - Kew Gardens, 1921-1934 (Box 5)
        - Floyd A McClure (China), 1926-1949 (Box 5)
        - Elmer D. Merrill (P.I., Calif.), 1918-1924 (Box 5)
        - Elmer D. Merrill (Calif.,), 1925-1929 (Box 5)
        - Elmer D. Merrill (N.Y., Arnold Arb.), 1930-1952 (Box 6)
        - Gwendolen Newell (Calif.), 1929-1950 (Box 6)
        - Ernest J. Palmer (Arnold Arb.), 1923-1952 (Box 6)
        - Harold E. Parks (Calif.), 1925-1929 (Box 6)
        - Flora W. Patterson (B.P.I.), 1921-1922 (Box 6)
        - Eduardo Quisumbing (P.I.), 1928-1953 (Box 6)
        - Alfred B. Rendle (Brit. Mus.), 1929 (Box 6)
        - Jose Santos (Box 6)
        - William A. Setchell (Calif.), 1921 (Box 6)
        - Chris Slattery (Box 6)
        - Effie S. Spalding (Calif.), 1924-1937 (Box 6)
        - Roland Thaxter (Harvard), 1924 (Box 6)
        - D. LeRoy Topping, 1915-1934 (Box 6)
        - E.Grace Ward (Calif.), 1924 (Box 6)
        - Cyril T. White (Brisbane), 1924-1950 (Box 6)
      - Clements Library (Randolph Adams; Howard Peckham) (Box 6)
      - Clialt, Gladys, 1912 (Box 6)
        (personal-Georgia)
      - Clover, Elzada U., 1931-1948 (Box 6)
        (student; faculty; collector)
      - Cobb, Frieda (Box 6)
      - Cobbe, Tom, 1945-1958 (Box 6)
        (student; A.F. collecting; positions)
      - Cockbill, Gerald F., 1955 (Box 6)
      - Cockrell, Robert A., 1934-1947 (Box 6)
        (Sumatran woods)